A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1952-1957 FA425
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1952
  - France, 1952; 1952/500
    - France - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/500.S
      - France, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 276)
  - Vietnam, 1952; 1952/509
    - Vietnam, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 276)
  - Society Islands, 1952; 1952/520
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes Tahiti
    - Tahiti, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 276)
  - Asia, 1952; 1952/600
    - Asia - Administration - (A-Z), 1952 (Box 44, Folder 277)
    - Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952; 1952/600.D
      - Asia, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 277)
    - Asia - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/600.S
      - Asia, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 277)
  - China, 1952; 1952/601
    - China - (A-Z), 1952 (Box 44, Folder 278)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/601.R
      - China, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 278)
  - Taiwan, 1952; 02.1952/605
    - Taiwan - (A-Z), 1952 (Box 44, Folder 279)
    - Taiwan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952; 1952/605.D
      - Taiwan, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 279)
    - Taiwan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/605.E
      - Taiwan, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 279)
    - Taiwan - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/605.R
      - Taiwan, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 279)
  - Japan, 1952; 1952/609
    - Japan - Administration, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 280)
    - Japan - (A-I), 1952 (Box 45, Folder 281)
    - Japan - (I-Ka), 1952 (Box 45, Folder 282)
    - Japan - (Ke-Pz), 1952 (Box 45, Folder 283)
    - Japan - (Q-Z), 1952 (Box 45, Folder 284)
    - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1952; 1952/609.A
      - Japan, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 285)
    - Japan - Nursing, 1952; 1952/609.C
      - Japan, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 285)
    - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952; 1952/609.D
      - Japan, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 285)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/609.E
      - Japan, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 285)
    - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/609.R
      - Japan, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 285)
    - Japan - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/609.S
      - Japan, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 285)
  - Korea, 1952; 1952/613
    - Korea, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 286)
    - Korea - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952; 1952/613.D
      - Korea, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 286)
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/613.E
      - Korea, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 286)
    - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/613.R
      - Korea, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 286)
  - Thailand, 1952; 1952/617
    - Thailand, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 287)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1952; 1952/617.A
      - Thailand, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 287)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952; 1952/617.D
      - Thailand, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 287)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/617.E
      - Thailand, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 287)
  - Southeast Asia, 1952; 1952/625
    - South East Asia, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 287)
  - Holland (Netherlands), 1952; 1952/650
    - Netherlands, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 288)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 289)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Declinations, 1952; 1952/650.F
      - Netherlands, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 289)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/650.R
      - Netherlands, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 289)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/650.S
      - Netherlands, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 289)
  - Indonesia, 1952; 1952/652
    - Indonesia, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 290)
    - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/652.R
      - Indonesia, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 290)
  - Java, 1952; 1952/655
    - Java, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 290)
  - Europe, 1952; 1952/700
    - Europe, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 290)
    - Europe - Nursing, 1952; 1952/700.C
      - Europe, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 290)
  - Afghanistan, 1952; 1952/703
    - Afghanistan, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 290)
  - Austria, 1952; 02.1952/705
    - Austria - (A-Z), 1952 (Box 46, Folder 291)
    - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1952; 1952/705.A
      - Austria, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 291)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/705.E
      - Austria, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 291)
    - Austria - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/705.S
      - Austria, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 291)
  - Belgium, 1952; 02.1952/707
    - Belgium, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 292)
    - Belgium - Nursing, 1952; 1952/707.C
      - Belgium, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 292)
  - Yugoslavia, 1952; 1952/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 292)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 292)
    - Yugoslavia - Public Health Education, 1952; 1952/710.L
      - Yugoslavia, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 292)
  - Bulgaria, 1952; 1952/711
    - Bulgaria, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 292)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1952; 1952/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 292)
  - Denmark, 1952; 1952/713
    - Denmark, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 293)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/713.E
      - Denmark, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 293)
    - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/713.R
      - Denmark, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 293)
  - Scandinavia, 1952; 1952/716
    - Scandinavia, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 293)
  - Germany, 1952; 1952/717
    - Germany - (A-Uk), 1952 (Box 47, Folder 294)
    - Germany - (A-Uk), 1952 (Box 47, Folder 295)
    - Germany - (Un-Z), 1952 (Box 47, Folder 296)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1952; 1952/717.A
      - Germany, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 297)
    - Germany - Nursing, 1952; 1952/717.C
      - Germany, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 297)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/717.E
      - Germany, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 297)
    - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/717.R
      - Germany, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 297)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1952; 02.1952/717.S
      - Germany, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 297)
  - Greece, 1952; 1952/749
    - Greece, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 298)
  - Hungary, 1952; 1952/750
    - Hungary, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 298)
  - Italy, 1952; 1952/751
    - Italy - (A-R), 1952 (Box 47, Folder 299)
    - Italy - (S-Z), 1952 (Box 48, Folder 300)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/751.E
      - Italy, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 300)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/751.S
      - Italy, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 300)
  - Norway, 1952; 1952/767
    - Norway, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 301)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/767.E
      - Norway, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 301)
  - Iran, 1952; 1952/771
    - Iran, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 302)
    - Iran - Nursing, 1952; 02.1952/771.C
      - Iran, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 302)
    - Iran - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/771.E
      - Iran, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 302)
  - Portugal, 1952; 1952/773
    - Portugal, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 303)
    - Portugal - Nursing, 1952; 1952/773.C
      - Portugal, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 303)
  - Rumania, 1952; 1952/783
    - Rumania, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 303)
  - Ukraine, 1952; 1952/784
    - Ukrania, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 303)
  - U.S.S.R., 1952; 1952/785
    - USSR, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 303)
    - U.S.S.R. - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/785.S
      - USSR, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 303)
  - Latvia, 1952; 1952/786
    - Latvia, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 303)
  - Finland, 1952; 1952/787
    - Finland, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - Finland - Nursing, 1952; 1952/787.C
      - Finland, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 304)
  - Poland, 1952; 1952/789
    - Poland, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1952; 1952/789.A
      - Poland, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/789.E
      - Poland, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - Poland - Declinations, 1952; 1952/789.F
      - Poland, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 304)
  - Spain, 1952; 1952/795
    - Spain, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - Spain - Medical Sciences, 1952; 1952/795.A
      - Spain, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 304)
  - Sweden, 1952; 1952/800
    - Sweden - (A-T), 1952 (Box 48, Folder 305)
    - Sweden - (U-Z), 1952 (Box 48, Folder 306)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1952; 1952/800.A
      - Sweden, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 307)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/800.E
      - Sweden, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 307)
    - Sweden - Declinations, 1952; 1952/800.F
      - Sweden, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 307)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/800.R
      - Sweden, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 308)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/800.S
      - Sweden, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 308)
  - Switzerland, 1952; 1952/803
    - Switzerland, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 309)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 310)
  - Near East Region, 1952; 1952/804
    - Near East, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 310)
    - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/804.R
      - Near East - Marshall, John - "Diary of a Trip to the Near East", February 10-April 3, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 311)
  - Turkey, 1952; 1952/805
    - Turkey, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 312)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/805.E
      - Turkey, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 313)
    - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/805.R
      - Turkey, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 313)
    - Turkey - Social Sciences, 1952; 1952/805.S
      - Turkey, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 313)
  - Cyprus, 1952; 1952/809
    - Cyprus, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 313)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1952; 1952/816
    - Saudi Arabia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/816.E
      - Saudi Arabia, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 313)
  - Israel, 1952; 1952/825
    - Israel, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 313)
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 1952; 1952/825.A
      - Israel, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 313)
  - Lebanon, 1952; 1952/833
    - Lebanon - (A-Z), 1952 (Box 49, Folder 314)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1952; 1952/833.C
      - Lebanon, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 315)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1952; 1952/833.E
      - Lebanon, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 315)
    - Lebanon - Humanities and Arts, 1952; 1952/833.R
      - Lebanon, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 315)
- General Correspondence, 1953
  - International, 1953; 1953/100
    - Aitken, Thomas H.G. - Anderson, Charles R., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Richmond K. - Anderson, R.K. - Publications, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Balfour, Marshall C., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Barnard, Chester I. - Belknap, Chauncey - Bevier, George, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Brackett, Elizabeth W., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bugher, John C. - Burden, Robert P., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Carr, Henry P., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Causey, Ottis R., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - D'Arms, Edward F. - DeVinney, Leland C., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Diplomatic Services - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Diplomatic Services - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Downs, Wilbur G. - Elmendorf, John E. - Fahs, Charles B., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Gilpatric, Chadbourne - Grant, John B. - Gregg, Alan, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Hahn, Richard G., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Harrar, J. George, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Harrar, J. George - "Survey Material for Far East trip, 1953" (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Hayes, Guy S., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Hill, Rolla B. - Hirst, Esther Mary, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - International - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - International - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Janney, John H. - Johnson, Harold N., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Johnson, Lillian, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Kerr, J. Austin - Kendrick, John F., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Kimball, Lindsley F., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Knipe, Fred W., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Lee, Ivy - Logan, John A., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - McCoy, Oliver R., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - McIntosh, W.A., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Maier, John, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Marshall, John - Miller, Harry M., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Morison, Robert S. - Ohlson, Virginia M., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Oliver, Wade - Payne, George C. - Peterson, Osler L. - Pomerat, Gerard R. - Rusk, Dean, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Russell, Paul F. - (1), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Russell, Paul F. - (2), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Ryan, Bryce - Sasse, Bruce E. - Smith, Hugh H., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Smithburn, K.C., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Strode, George K. - Struthers, R.R., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Taylor, Richard M., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - United Nations - (A-UNESCO), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - UNESCO - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - United Nations - (F-H), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - United Nations - (I-We), 1953 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - United Nations - (I-We), 1953 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - United Nations - World Health Organization, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Warren, Andrew J., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Watson, Robert B., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Watson, Robert B., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Watson, Robert B., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Weaver, Warren - Webb, Vanderbilt, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Weir, John M. - Wilson, D. Bruce, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Work, Telford W., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Worth, C. Brooke, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous - (A-B), 1953 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous - (C), 1953 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous - (D-Ec), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous - (Ed-G), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous - (H-K), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous - (L-Mag), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous - (Mai-O), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous - (P-Ro), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous - (Ru-Sm), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Miscellaneous - (So-Ta), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Miscellaneous - (Te-Wel), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1953; 1953/100.A
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - International - Nursing, 1953; 1953/100.C
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - International - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1953; 1953/100.E
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - International - Social Science Fellows, 1953; 1953/100.ES
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - International - Medicine and Public Health Fellows, 1953; 1953/100.EY
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1953; 1953/100.O
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1953; 1953/100.S
      - Miscellaneous - (Wer-Z), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - United States, 1953; 1953/200
    - United States - Aa-Al, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - United States - Aa-Al, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - United States - American A-Co, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - United States - American Council on Education, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - United States - American Council on Education, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - United States - American D-F, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - United States - American H-Ph, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - United States - American Political Science Association, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - United States - American Psychiatric Association - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - United States - American Ps-Z, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - United States - Am-As, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - United States - (As-Ca), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - United States - (As-Ca), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - United States - (As-Ca), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - United States - (As-Ca), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - United States - (As-Ca), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - United States - (As-Ca), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - United States - Carnegie Corporation, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - United States - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - United States - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - United States - Ce-Col, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - United States - Ce-Col, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - United States - Ce-Col, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - United States - Columbia University - (A-R), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - United States - Columbia University - (A-R), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - United States - Columbia University - (S-Z), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - United States - Com-Cons, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - United States - Conservation Foundation, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - United States - Cons-Cop, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 94)
    - United States - Cornell University - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 95)
    - United States - Cornell University - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - United States - Cos-Cz, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - United States - Da-Fol, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 98)
    - United States - Da-Fol, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 99)
    - United States - Da-Fol, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 100)
    - United States - Da-Fol, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 101)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 102)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 103)
    - United States - For-Hart, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - United States - For-Hart, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - United States - For-Hart, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - United States - For-Hart, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - United States - For-Hart, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 108)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-D), 1953 (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - United States - Harvard University - (E-Z), 1953 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - United States - Harvard University - (E-Z), 1953 (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - United States - Harvard University - (E-Z), 1953 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - United States - He-Inst, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - United States - He-Inst, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - United States - He-Inst, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - United States - Institute - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 116)
    - United States - Institute - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 117)
    - United States - Int-Le, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 118)
    - United States - Int-Le, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 119)
    - United States - Int-Le, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 120)
    - United States - Int-Le, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 121)
    - United States - Int-Le, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 122)
    - United States - Li-Med, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 123)
    - United States - Li-Med, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 124)
    - United States - Li-Med, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 125)
    - United States - Li-Med, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 126)
    - United States - Meharry Medical College - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 20, Folder 127)
    - United States - Mel-Mz, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 128)
    - United States - Mel-Mz, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 129)
    - United States - Na, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 130)
    - United States - National - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 21, Folder 131)
    - United States - National - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 21, Folder 132)
    - United States - National - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 21, Folder 133)
    - United States - National - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 21, Folder 134)
    - United States - Ne-New, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 135)
    - United States - Ni-Pre, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 136)
    - United States - Ni-Pre, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 137)
    - United States - Ni-Pre, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 138)
    - United States - Ni-Pre, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 139)
    - United States - Ni-Pre, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 140)
    - United States - Princeton University - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 22, Folder 141)
    - United States - Pr-Se, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 142)
    - United States - Pr-Se, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 143)
    - United States - Pr-Se, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 144)
    - United States - Pr-Se, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 145)
    - United States - Pr-Se, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 146)
    - United States - Pr-Se, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 147)
    - United States - Sh-Un, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 148)
    - United States - Sh-Un, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 149)
    - United States - Sh-Un, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 150)
    - United States - Sh-Un, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 151)
    - United States - Sh-Un, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 152)
    - United States - United States - Agriculture - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 24, Folder 153)
    - United States - United States - (A-Ce), 1953 (Box 24, Folder 154)
    - United States - United States - (Ci-N), 1953 (Box 25, Folder 155)
    - United States - United States - (Ci-N), 1953 (Box 25, Folder 156)
    - United States - United States - Point Four Program, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 157)
    - United States - United States Public Health Service, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 158)
    - United States - United States Public Health Service, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 159)
    - United States - United States - (S-Z), 1953 (Box 25, Folder 160)
    - United States - United States - (S-Z), 1953 (Box 25, Folder 161)
    - United States - University - (A-B), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 162)
    - United States - University of California - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 163)
    - United States - University of California - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 164)
    - United States - University of California - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 165)
    - United States - University of Chattanooga, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 166)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 167)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 168)
    - United States - University - (Ci-H), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 169)
    - United States - University of Illinois - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 27, Folder 170)
    - United States - University - (Io-Z), 1953 (Box 27, Folder 171)
    - United States - University - (Io-Z), 1953 (Box 27, Folder 172)
    - United States - University - (Io-Z), 1953 (Box 27, Folder 173)
    - United States - Va-Vin, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 174)
    - United States - (Vio-Wz), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 175)
    - United States - (Vio-Wz), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 176)
    - United States - (Vio-Wz), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 177)
    - United States - (Vio-Wz), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 178)
    - United States - Yale University - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 179)
    - United States - (Y-Z), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 180)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1953; 1953/200.A
      - United States - (A-T), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 181)
      - United States - University - (A-V), 1953 (Box 29, Folder 182)
      - United States - University - (A-V), 1953 (Box 29, Folder 183)
      - United States - University of Washington Medical School, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 184)
      - United States - (Up-Z), 1953 (Box 29, Folder 185)
    - United States - Nursing, 1953; 1953/200.C
      - United States - (Up-Z), 1953 (Box 29, Folder 186)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1953; 1953/200.D
      - United States - (Up-Z), 1953 (Box 29, Folder 186)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1953; 1953/200.E
      - United States - (Up-Z), 1953 (Box 29, Folder 186)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1953; 1953/200.R
      - United States - (A-N), 1953 (Box 29, Folder 187)
      - United States - (O-Z), 1953 (Box 30, Folder 188)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1953; 1953/200.S
      - United States - (A-R), 1953 (Box 30, Folder 189)
      - United States - Social Science Research Council - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 30, Folder 190)
      - United States - Social Science Research Council - (A-Z), 1953 (Box 30, Folder 191)